<add>
<doc>
  <field name = "id">1</field>
  <field name = "title>">Mathematical modelling and improvement of operating practices of sun drying of rice: a thesis presented in partial fulfilment of the requirements for the degree of Doctor of Phylosophy [i.e. Philosophy] at Massey University</field>
  <field name = "subject">rice</field>
  <field name = "text">  In Cambodia, sun drying of rice has always been of great importance for preserving rice. The main goal of this study was to find the conditions for sun drying that maximise the throughput while minimising quality loss. A whole-bed approach was taken to investigate the conditions of the grain and the air at different layers during the drying process. Seven sets of sun-drying experiments were conducted in Cambodia using a range of methods practiced by rice farmers. These methods included drying with different bed depths (2 to 6 cm), with the bed on different pads (water-proof tarpaulin, mat, net, polystyIn Cambodia, sun drying of rice has always been of great importance for preserving rice. The main goal of this study was to find the conditions for sun drying that maximise the throughput while minimising quality loss. A whole-bed approach was taken to investigate the conditions of the grain and the air at different layers during the drying process. Seven sets of sun-drying experiments were conducted in Cambodia using a range of methods practiced by rice farmers. These methods included drying with different bed depths (2 to 6 cm), with the bed on different pads (water-proof tarpaulin, mat, net, polystyIn Cambodia, sun drying of rice has always been of great importance for preserving rice. The main goal of this study was to find the conditions for sun drying that maximise the throughput while minimising quality loss. A whole-bed approach was taken to investigate the conditions of the grain and the air at different layers during the drying process. Seven sets of sun-drying experiments were conducted in Cambodia using a range of methods practiced by rice farmers. These methods included drying with different bed depths (2 to 6 cm), with the bed on different pads (water-proof tarpaulin, mat, net, polystyIn Cambodia, sun drying of rice has always been of great importance for preserving rice. The main goal of this study was to find the conditions for sun drying that maximise the throughput while minimising quality loss. A whole-bed approach was taken to investigate the conditions of the grain and the air at different layers during the drying process. Seven sets of sun-drying experiments were conducted in Cambodia using a range of methods practiced by rice farmers. These methods included drying with different bed depths (2 to 6 cm), with the bed on different pads (water-proof tarpaulin, mat, net, polysty</field>
</doc>
<doc>
  <field name = "id">2</field>
  <field name = "title>">Doing other stuf </field> 
  <field name = "subject">dogs</field>
  <field name = "text"> lorme ipsum so there are not that many people who care about keyboards, or GMK keyboards specifically.</field>
</doc>
</add>
